WILDAN JAYA KUSOEMA

West Java, Indonesia | wildanjk14@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/wildan-jaya-kusoema-7954741a0/ | https://github.com/Wz-00/ | https://wz-portfolio.vercel.app/

ABOUT ME

Computer science fresh graduate with an interest in backend developer. Experience on Full-stack web developer internship which strengthens my skills in Database management, RESTful API, MVC architecture, and JWT auth. Accustomed to working with a team and any tools, especially GIT, MySQL, Object oriented programming and procedural programming. Ready to contribute to the backend development team with a high learning spirit and good adaptability.

EDUCATION

STMIK INDONESIA MANDIRI

(October 2021 – Now)

Bachelor of Computer Science (GPA: 3.29/4.0)

Majoring in Computer Science and got solid skill in any backend language, restful api, MySQL DBMS, and familiar to scrum method. I learnt how to design web, developing frontend or backend web app, database design, and any technologies for support business project.

• CyberSecurity Training

(2021)

Infradigital Foundation

As a cybersecurity student, I've learnt CompTIA Linux+, CompTIA Security+, and CompTIA CySA+, providing me to help to secure web business.

EXPERIENCE

CyberLabs

(October 2024 – December 2024)

Fullstack Web Developer - intern

As a fullstack web developer, I responsible to create safe and functional website logic (backend), and responsive web.

ORGANIZATION

Student Executive Board (BEM)

(January 2024 - December 2024)

Minister of the Department of Sports

- Identifying student interests and talents in sports
- Coordinating Student Activity Units in the field of sports
- Leading and coordinating department members in the department's work program

SKILLS

- **Teamwork**: Be able to work as a team collaboratively and effectively
- Communication: Have good communication skills both verbally and in writing
- Programming Language: PHP, JavaScript (also Node.js), Python
- Database/ DBMS: Mysql
- Framework: Laravel, Codelgniter, Express.js, React.js
- Tools: Git/Github, Gitlab, Laragon, MySQL Workbench, Postman.